morange.com 2010-06-06

# Privacy Policy - MoRange V

**OVERVIEW**  
MoRange takes your privacy seriously. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the websites provided by Morange. 

**CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY**  
The terms and conditions of the Terms of Service are incorporated herein by reference. By agreeing to the Terms of Service, you consent to the collection and use of information about you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
Registration: Morange, we will request some personal information, including your first and last name, your cell phone number and model, gender, age, country and your cellular carrier to create your account. For the purpose for providing the MoRange services, we may need you to provide your email address and password, instant messaging account ID and password. We use your registration information to manage your account and to provide you with the MoRange Services. Therefore, when you register as a member of Morange, you represent that you are providing complete and accurate information. 

_Email:_

We place email links on this Site to allow you to contact us directly. The information you provide is used to respond directly to your questions or comments, and is subject to the Terms of Service. We may also file your comments to improve the Site and our Services, or review and discard the information. 

_General:_

MoRange uses information collected from you for the following general purposes: fulfill your requests for Services; improve our Services; contact you to resolve problems; conduct research; meet legal and regulatory requirements; and make this Site easier to use by reducing the need for you to enter information. 

**COOKIES**  
In order to provide you with personalized service, MoRange uses "cookies" to keep and occasionally track information. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. The cookies that are gathered by MoRange are only used by Morange. At NO time do we share information from cookies with third parties.   
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your password if you choose "auto login", so you don't have to enter it more than once. We also store your display resolution and whether JavaScript is enabled in your browser to enhance the experience on our Site. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's help file. However, removing cookies may not allow you to take full advantage of all MoRange features. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
Please note that, while using Morange, you could be directed to another site which is developed by people over whom MoRange exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.   
When you link to another site, you should review their privacy policy, as it may be different from our Privacy Policy. MoRange is not responsible, and shall not be liable, for the privacy practices of linked sites or any use such sites may make of any information collected from you. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Site. 

**INFORMATION SHARING**  
MoRange does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

1\. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 

2\. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MoRange 's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

3\. We transfer information about you if MoRange is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MoRange will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

4\. We may use the information to communicate with you about our Services and to notify you of other MoRange services that may be of interest. 

**AGGREGATE DATA**  
When you access Morange.com, our server automatically collects certain information that is not personally identifiable, such as your IP address, emails submitted, pages viewed, and length of time spent on the website. We collect and use this information, in the aggregate only, to diagnose problems with out server and to improve Morange.com and the Services.

**UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION**  
We provide mechanisms for you to review and update your personal information through the MoRange website. If you wish to review or update your information, visit the MoRange website and click Login. 

**INFORMATION SECURITY**  
MoRange exercises reasonable efforts to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that such information will be protected from actions outside of our control, such as computer hacking and physical theft. You acknowledge that you provide your personal information at your own risk.   
**  
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**   
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting notice of the change on the Site. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective thirty days following our posting of notice of the changes on the Site. Your continued use of the Services and the Site constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
